Hey.
嘿。
what happened?
發生了什麼？
Ne var?
內瓦爾？
We got a withdrawal order. They are closing the program.
我們收到了提款令。 他們正在關閉該程序。
They say we're behind
他們說我們落後了
In the deal we made ﻿for the Mark 10 .
在我們為 Mark 10 達成的交易中。
Two more months until Mark 10.
還有兩個月，直到馬克 10。
And these tests are for the Mark 9.
這些測試適用於 Mark 9。
That wasn't good enough.
那還不夠好。
- Who says? - Admiral Cane.
- 誰說？ - 甘蔗上將。
Drone fighter.
無人機戰鬥機。
He wants our budget transferred to his drone program.
他希望我們的預算轉移到他的無人機項目上。
He's coming here to terminate the ﻿Program himself .
他來這裡是為了親自終止程序。
What can we do?
我們能做什麼？
Does he want Mark 10?
他想要馬克10嗎？
Let's give him the Mark 10.
讓我們給他馬克 10。
Let me inform you again. The deal is for the Mark-10.
讓我再次通知你。 這筆交易適用於 Mark-10。
Not 10.1, not 10.2.
不是 10.1，不是 10.2。
Mark-10.
馬克-10。
This keeps the program alive.
這使程序保持活力。
I don't like that look, man.
我不喜歡那個樣子，伙計。
I only have this view.
我只有這個觀點。
Control, this is Dark Star. What are the values?
控制，這裡是暗星。 價值觀是什麼？
He can hear the control sound just fine . And you?
他能聽到控制聲音就好了。 你呢？
Pretty clear. Let's move on to the departure procedure.
很清楚。 讓我們繼續出發程序。
I'm ready for ATU, sir.
先生，我已經為 ATU 做好了準備。
Rear left engine running.
左後發動機運轉。
Rear right engine is running.
右後發動機正在運轉。
Acceleration confirmation?
加速確認？
We are ready to accelerate.
我們準備加速。
Dark Star's main engines are ready for takeoff.
暗星的主引擎已準備好起飛。
Dark Star's engines are active.
暗星的引擎已啟動。
It's on track 2. Its course is 2-1-0-1-0.
它在第 2 條軌道上。它的路線是 2-1-0-1-0。
Engine temperature seems fine. Check confirmed.
發動機溫度似乎很好。 檢查確認。
Dark Star is at 95% power and pressure looks good.
暗星的功率為 95%，壓力看起來不錯。
Check confirmed.
檢查確認。
From Dark Star to Tower. We're ready to take off and we're asking permission.
從暗星到塔。 我們準備起飛，我們正在徵求許可。
Dark Star, the runway is yours.
暗星，跑道是你的。
Are you Admiral Chester Cain?
你是海軍上將切斯特凱恩嗎？
Maverick, Cain has just entered the base.
特立獨行，該隱剛剛進入基地。
It's not too late to stop, man.
停止還為時不晚，伙計。
You know what will happen to you if you keep going.
如果你繼續前進，你知道會發生什麼。
I know what will happen to you if I don't.
如果我不這樣做，我知道你會發生什麼。
Dark Star is ready to take off.
暗星準備起飛。
Everyone, prepare to take off.
大家準備起飛。
Let's start with the engines.
讓我們從引擎開始。
- The engines are ready. - Thermal ready.
- 引擎已準備就緒。 - 熱準備。
- Fuel is ready. - Mid engine ready.
- 燃料已準備好。 - 中置引擎準備就緒。
- Control units are ready. - Dark Star, you've received clearance.
- 控制單元已準備就緒。 - 暗星，你已獲得許可。
All right, honey.
好吧，親愛的。
One last ride.
最後一程。
Dark Star, you're allowed to go above 600 feet.
暗星，你可以飛到 600 英尺以上。
Ascend 3.5 miles.
上升 3.5 英里。
I'm leaving 600 feet.
我要離開 600 英尺。
I'm climbing 3.5 miles.
我正在爬 3.5 英里。
Amiral...
上將...
- Just in time, sir. - Your time is up.
- 及時，先生。 - 你的時間到了。
Do you have an explanation?
你有解釋嗎？
I'm switching to the Seram jet.
我正在切換到 Seram 噴氣機。
- Mav wants Admiral Cain... - He commands.
- Mav 想要 Cain 上將... - 他發號施令。
He orders... that we take it down.
他命令……我們把它拿下來。
Alfa... Green...
阿爾法...綠色...
Forward... value...
轉發...價值...
And mark... target...
並標記...目標...
That 's the problem we're having with communication , sir.
這就是我們在溝通方面遇到的問題，先生。
Sometimes parasites can occur. We are still trying to solve it.
有時會出現寄生蟲。 我們仍在努力解決它。
Has anyone offered you coffee?
有人請你喝咖啡嗎？
Pekala.
佩卡拉。
Currently on Mark-7. It's pushing 8.
目前在 Mark-7 上。 它正在推動8。
- Flight data? - Receiving. Data is in good condition.
- 航班數據？ - 接收。 數據狀況良好。
The temperature is rising. Values ​​are still stable.
溫度正在上升。 數值還是比較穩定的。
We will not have any problems.
我們不會有任何問題。
Mark-8.8.
馬克-8.8。
8.9.
8.9。
Locked to 9.0.
鎖定到 9.0。
He is the fastest man alive.
他是世界上最快的人。
Talk to me, Goose.
跟我說話，鵝。
Mark 9.1.
標記 9.1。
Mark 9.3.
標記 9.3。
Mark 9.4.
標記 9.4。
Approaching high hypersonic velocity.
接近高超音速。
Windshield heat shield.
擋風玻璃隔熱罩。
The surface temperature is rising.
表面溫度正在上升。
Come on, honey. A little more.
來吧，親愛的。 再來一點。
a little more.
再來一點。
Hadi!
哈迪！
- Mark 10! - Yes!
- 標記 10！ - 是的！
Take your budget cut!!
削減預算！！
Efendim.
埃芬迪姆。
Don't do it. Do not do this...
不要做。 不要這樣做...
Sadece...
薩迪斯...
... a little push...
……輕輕一推……
Hassiktir be...
哈西克提爾...
It takes balls to do this.
做到這一點需要球。
You have to give your due.
你必須付出你應得的。
PRESS TO RESET MAIN ALARM
按下以重置主警報
Hassiktir...
哈西克提爾...
Maverick?
特立獨行？
Thank you.
謝謝你。
Neredeyim ben?
內雷德伊姆本？
İrlanda.
愛爾蘭。
Maverick.
特立獨行。
More than 30 years of service.
服務超過 30 年。
War medals. Notifications...
戰爭勳章。 通知...
The only man to have shot down 3 enemy planes in the last 40 years.
過去 40 年來唯一擊落 3 架敵機的人。
Outstanding effort.
傑出的努力。
But you don't get promoted.
但是你沒有得到晉升。
You are not retiring.
你沒有退休。
And no matter how hard you try , you refuse to die.
而且無論你怎麼努力，你都拒絕死。
You should at least be a two-star admiral by now.
你現在至少應該是個二星上將了。
Or a senator.
或者參議員。
But here you are.
但是你來了。
Yüzbaşı.
尤茲巴什。
Why is that?
這是為什麼？
That's one of life's mysteries , sir.
這是人生的奧秘之一，先生。
This is not a joke. I asked you a question.
這不是一個玩笑。 我問了你一個問題。
I'm where I belong, sir.
我是屬於我的地方，先生。
The Navy doesn't see it that way.
海軍不這麼看。
Not anymore.
不再。
Those planes you're testing , Captain...
你正在測試的那些飛機，機長...
Someday soon there will be no need for pilots at all.
很快有一天，根本不需要飛行員。
To the pilots who need to ﻿sleep, eat, pee.
給需要睡覺、吃飯、撒尿的飛行員。
To the pilots who disobeyed orders.
對於不服從命令的飛行員。
All you did was buy those guys out there some time.
你所做的只是讓那些傢伙出去一段時間。
But the future is on its way.
但未來正在路上。
And you are not in it.
而你不在其中。
Best to send these guys from base.
最好從基地派出這些傢伙。
take to headquarters.
帶到總部。
Say goodbye to them ﻿while you pack your things .
在你收拾東西的時候跟他們說再見。
I want them on their way to Northern Ireland in an hour .
我要他們在一小時內前往北愛爾蘭。
To Northern Ireland, sir?
去北愛爾蘭，先生？
A call came ﻿at the perfect time .
一個電話在完美的時間打來。
Just when I came here to punish you forever.
就在我來這里永遠懲罰你的時候。
I don't feel comfortable saying that.
我不喜歡這樣說。
But I can say that he owes ﻿his guardian angel .
但我可以說，他欠他的守護天使。
You've been recalled to Top Gun.
你已被召回壯志凌雲。
- Sir? - You can go, Captain.
- 先生？ - 你可以走了，船長。
Penultimate, none, Maverick.
倒數第二，沒有，特立獨行。
Your species is doomed to extinction.
你們的物種注定要滅絕。
It may be so, sir.
可能是這樣，先生。
But not today.
但不是今天。
San Diego, Califomia Fightertown U.S.A
聖地亞哥，加利福尼亞州 Fightertown U.S.A
Pacific Fleet Naval Air Force
太平洋艦隊海軍空軍
Tom "Iceman" Kazansky , Commander of the Pacific Fleet
太平洋艦隊司令湯姆“冰人”卡贊斯基
Yüzbaşı Pete "Maverick" Mitchell.
Yüzbaşı皮特“特立獨行”米切爾。
Your fame precedes you.
你的名聲在你之前。
Thank you, sir.
謝謝你，先生。
It wasn't a compliment.
這不是恭維。
Ben Amiral Beau Simpson. Hava patronuyum.
本·阿米拉爾·博·辛普森。 哈瓦守護神。
Yardımcım Solomon Bates.
Yardımcım 所羅門·貝茨。
Warlock, sir?
術士，先生？
I have to say I didn't expect to be called back .
我不得不說我沒想到會被召回。
These are called "orders" , Maverick.
這些被稱為“命令”，Maverick。
You two have something in common.
你們兩個有共同點。
The "Cyclone" next to me was best-in-class in 1988.
我旁邊的“旋風”是 1988 年同類產品中最好的。
I actually finished second, sir.
我實際上獲得了第二名，先生。
I just wanted to meet expectations .
我只是想滿足期望。
Let's get to the goal.
讓我們達到目標。
An unauthorized uranium enrichment plant.
未經授權的鈾濃縮廠。
It was built in violation ﻿of numerous NATO agreements .
它的建造違反了許多北約協議。
The uranium produced there...
那裡生產的鈾...
... poses a direct threat to ﻿our allies in the region .
... 對我們在該地區的盟友構成直接威脅。
The Pentagon has given us the task of forming an assault team to ﻿destroy it .
五角大樓給了我們組建突擊隊來摧毀它的任務。
before it is ﻿fully operational .
在它完全運行之前。
The facility is located in an underground bunker ﻿behind this mountain .
該設施位於這座山後面的地下掩體中。
GPS does not work in the valley and is surrounded by heat-seeking missiles.
GPS在山谷中不起作用，被尋熱導彈包圍。
There are also a limited number of 5th generation fighters in the vicinity.
附近還有數量有限的第五代戰鬥機。
There are attack helicopters and vintage aircraft for support purposes.
有攻擊直升機和老式飛機用於支持目的。
There are even a few old F-14s.
甚至還有幾架舊的 F-14。
I guess we were the only ones who ﻿couldn't get rid of nostalgia .
我想我們是唯一無法擺脫懷舊的人。
What is your assessment, Captain?
你的評價是什麼，船長？
Sir, normally..
先生，通常..
... with the F-35s flying in silent mode , this would be child's play.
...在 F-35 以靜音模式飛行時，這將是兒戲。
But not working GPS throws it away.
但是不工作的 GPS 會把它扔掉。
The threat on the surface appears to be small.
表面上的威脅似乎很小。
Laser guided attack. I think it's achievable with an F-18.
激光制導攻擊。 我認為使用 F-18 是可以實現的。
Two bombs ﻿dropped right on target . Minimum.
兩枚炸彈正好落在目標上。 最低限度。
4 planes flying in pairs.
4 架飛機成對飛行。
There 's quite a ramp to get out of here.
離開這裡有一個相當大的坡道。
We'll be in the clear for the missiles ﻿at the summit .
在峰會上，我們將清楚地看到導彈。
Even if we get out of here...
即使我們離開這裡...
... there is a dogfight ﻿until we get home .
......有一場混戰直到我們回家。
You have everything you have learned from ﻿experience .
你擁有從經驗中學到的一切。
It's not the same task, sir.
先生，這不是同一個任務。
There seems to be no ﻿going back from this .
似乎沒有退路。
Can it be done or not?
能不能做？
How long does it take for the facility to become fully operational?
該設施需要多長時間才能完全投入使用？
three weeks. Maybe less.
3週。 也許更少。
It's been a while since I 've driven an F-18 and...
自從我駕駛 F-18 和...
...for the other three pilots, I'm not sure who I can trust.
...對於其他三名飛​​行員，我不確定我可以信任誰。
But I'm trying to find a way out.
但我正在努力尋找出路。
I think you misunderstood, Captain.
我想你誤會了，船長。
- Sir? - We're not asking you to fly.
- 先生？ - 我們不是要你飛。
We want a teacher.
我們要老師。
To teach, sir?
教授，先生？
We recruited the best 12 pilots from their battalions.
我們從他們的營中招募了最優秀的 12 名飛行員。
We want you to get your numbers down to 6 .
我們希望您將數字減少到 6 。
In the mission they will fly.
在任務中，他們將飛行。
Is there a problem, Captain?
有問題嗎，船長？
Do you know ﻿who he is , sir?
先生，您知道他是誰嗎？
Bradley Bradshaw.
布拉德利·布拉德肖。
Nicknamed "Rooster". You 've flown with his father before.
綽號“公雞”。 你以前和他父親一起飛過。
What was his nickname?
他的暱稱是什麼？
"Goose" efendim.
“鵝” efendim。
- What happened was so tragic. - There's something wrong with Captain Mitchell...
- 發生的事情太悲慘了。 - 米切爾船長出了點問題……
... it was determined that he did not do it and that his death was an accident.
......確定他沒有這樣做，他的死是一次意外。
What do you say, Captain?
你說什麼，船長？
Will you take Goose's son?
你會帶走Goose的兒子嗎？
With all due respect , I 'm not a teacher, sir.
恕我直言，先生，我不是老師。
You were a Top Gun instructor before.
你以前是一名壯志凌雲的教練。
That was 30 years ago and it took two months.
那是30年前的事了，花了兩個月的時間。
That's not my place.
那不是我的地方。
Let me be as clear as possible.
讓我盡可能清楚。
You were not my first choice. You're not the only one on the list.
你不是我的第一選擇。 你不是名單上的唯一一個。
You are here at the ﻿request of Admiral Kazansky .
您是應卡贊斯基海軍上將的要求來到這裡的。
Iceman is someone I respect a lot.
冰人是我非常尊敬的人。
He seems to think you have something left ﻿to offer the Navy .
他似乎認為你還有一些東西可以提供給海軍。
But I can't imagine it.
但我無法想像。
You don't have to accept this job.
你不必接受這份工作。
But let me be clear.
但讓我說清楚。
This will be your last mission, Captain.
這將是你的最後一個任務，船長。
You either fly for Top Gun, or you never fly again for the Navy.
你要么為壯志凌雲而飛，要么永遠不再為海軍飛。
It didn't go very well.
它進行得併不順利。
The child is not ready for this task.
孩子還沒有準備好完成這項任務。
Nobody?
沒有人？
That's why you're here.
這就是你在這裡的原因。
You could have warned me.
你本可以警告我的。
Would you come then?
那你會來嗎？
You must be kidding.
你一定在開玩笑。
Pete.
皮特。
Penny?
一分錢​​？
- What are you doing here? - I should ask you the same.
- 你在這裡做什麼？ - 我也應該問你。
It's a long story.
這是一個很長的故事。
- I doubt it. - Yes...
- 我對此表示懷疑。 - 是的...
- Who did you piss off this time? - Another Admiral.
- 這次你惹誰了？ - 另一位海軍上將。
It sure is.
確實是。
- Are you angry with me? - Oh, Pete...
- 你在生我的氣嗎？ - 哦，皮特...
I can never stay mad at you.
我永遠不能生你的氣。
That's the problem.
那就是問題所在。
I never thought I 'd run into ﻿you in Northern Ireland .
我從沒想過我會在北愛爾蘭遇到你。
- How long have you been here? - It's been 3 years since I bought this place.
- 你來這裡多久了？ - 我買這個地方已經 3 年了。
3 years?
3年？
Shortly after you angered the other Admiral and was driven into the desert .
不久後你激怒了另一位海軍上將並被趕進了沙漠。
Was this 3 years ago?
這是3年前嗎？
You must be in big trouble.
你一定遇到了大麻煩。
It is not possible for you to come here willingly .
你不可能心甘情願地來這裡。
Neyse...
奈斯...
You will find a way.
你會找到方法的。
No, I guess..
不，我猜..
I think I'm done.
我想我已經完成了。
Hadi, Pete.
哈迪，皮特。
I know you , you 're saying this since I got to know you.
我認識你，自從我認識你後，你就這麼說。
You said you'd take me for a ride in that F-18 .
你說過你會帶我乘坐那架 F-18。
And I saw that you are going to Bosnia.
我看到你要去波斯尼亞。
And Iraq.
還有伊拉克。
Both times.
兩次。
You got yourself in trouble.
你給自己惹了麻煩。
Iceman made a phone call and you're back here.
冰人打了個電話，你又回來了。
Penny, this is different.
佩妮，這不一樣。
Pete, trust me.
皮特，相信我。
Given the current odds...
鑑於目前的賠率...
somehow you'll be in a fighter plane ﻿with your tail on fire.
不知何故，您將乘坐戰鬥機，尾巴著火。
- Penny... - It's too late.
- 佩妮... - 太晚了
- What? - You're about to ask when I'm leaving.
- 什麼？ - 你要問我什麼時候走。
Don't give me that look.
不要給我那種眼神。
I'm not looking at you.
我不是在看你。
I swear.
我發誓。
The end is always the same for us, Pete.
皮特，我們的結局總是一樣的。
Let's not start this time.
這次我們不要開始。
Peki.
佩奇。
you look good.
你看起來挺好的。
Thank you very much, mate.
非常感謝你，伙計。
What am I missing?
我錯過了什麼？
- If you disrespect a woman or put her phone down... - Drinks are on you next.
- 如果你不尊重一個女人或放下她的電話... - 飲料是你的下一個。
Herkese mi?
赫克斯米？
Rules are rules, I'm afraid. You're lucky it's early.
規則就是規則，我害怕。 你很幸運，時間還早。
If so!
如果是這樣！
Who is that here?
這裡是誰？
Yüzbaşı Phoenix.
Yüzbaşı鳳凰城。
I thought they ﻿only got the specials here , Coyote.
我以為他們只在這裡買到特價商品，土狼。
It turns out that they were inviting anyone who came before them.
事實證明，他們是在邀請任何比他們先來的人。
- Gentlemen, this is friend Bagman. - Hangman.
- 先生們，這是巴格曼的朋友。 - 劊子手。
Well, anyway.
好吧，無論如何。
You're looking at the only Navy team that ﻿has taken down an enemy during active duty .
您正在查看唯一一支在現役期間擊落敵人的海軍團隊。
- Stop. - Came to mind...
- 停止。 - 想到了……
Yours is in a museum, right? from the Korean War.
你的在博物館裡，對吧？ 從朝鮮戰爭開始。
- Cold War. - It was in the same century, after all.
- 冷戰。 - 畢竟是在同一個世紀。
Not in this century.
本世紀沒有。
- Who are your friends? - Payback. - Fanboy.
- 你的朋友是誰？  - 回報。  - 粉絲。
- Hey, Coyote. - Hey.
- 嘿，郊狼。 - 嘿。
- Who is this? - Who is who?
- 這是誰？ - 誰是誰？
When did you come in?
你什麼時候進來的？
I was always here already.
我一直都在這裡。
- The man is a silent flight pilot. - Literally.
- 這個人是一個沉默的飛行員。 - 字面上地。
Weapons systems officer, actually.
實際上，武器系統官員。
With no sense of humor.
沒有幽默感。
- What do they call you? - Bob.
- 他們叫你什麼？ - 鮑勃。
No, that's your nickname.
不，那是你的暱稱。
Bob.
鮑勃。
Bob Floyd.
鮑勃弗洛伊德。
Will you sit behind me?
你會坐在我後面嗎？
- From LeMoire? - It seems so.
- 來自勒莫爾？ - 好像是這樣。
Masaya gel, Bob.
馬薩亞凝膠，鮑勃。
Vur hadi.
武爾哈迪。
Tamam.
塔瑪姆。
- Penny, dear? - Yes.
- 佩妮，親愛的？ - 是的。
You write ﻿four more on the old rifle .
你在舊步槍上又寫了四個。
Bradshaw!
布拉德肖！
is that you?
那是你嗎？
Is this how I would find out that you still fly ?
這就是我會發現你還在飛的方式嗎？
Yeah, I thought I'd ﻿surprise you .
是的，我想我會給你一個驚喜。
I guess I surprised you too.
我想我也讓你感到驚訝。
- Good to see you. - You too.
- 很高興見到你。 - 你也是。
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- 幹得好。 - 謝謝。
Thanks, daddy.
謝謝爸爸。
Shall we close the account before they rob me of it?
我們應該在他們搶走我之前關閉帳戶嗎？
Bradshaw? Bloody before me.
布拉德肖？ 血淋淋的在我面前。
hangman? You look good.
劊子手？ 你看起來挺好的。
İyiyim, Rooster.
İyiyim，公雞。
I am very good. Even...
我很好。 甚至...
I'm too good to be true.
我好得令人難以置信。
Do any of you know the subject of ﻿this special gathering ?
你們有人知道這次特別聚會的主題嗎？
Duty is duty.
義務就是義務。
It's not a problem for me.
這對我來說不是問題。
What I want to know... is who will be the team leader.
我想知道... 誰將成為團隊的領導者。
And which of you has what it takes.
你們誰有什麼需要。
to follow me.
跟著我。
Hangman, the only place to go after you is an early grave.
劊子手，追你的唯一地方是一個早期的墳墓。
If the one who follows you...
如果跟著你的人...
...runs out of fuel...
...燃料耗盡...
Do you remember last year , Rooster?
你還記得去年嗎，公雞？
He wanted so much to show ﻿himself in that test .
他非常想在那次測試中展示自己。
You were waiting for the right moment.
你在等待合適的時機。
The one who never came.
從未來過的那個。
I love this.
我喜歡這個。
This hasn't changed.
這沒有改變。
No. Unchanged.
不，不變。
Look at this.
看這個。
More pilots.
更多的飛行員。
Harvard, Yale, Omaha... Fuck it, that's Fritz.
哈佛、耶魯、奧馬哈……操，那是弗里茨。
What kind of task is this?
這是什麼任務？
That's not the question we should be asking.
這不是我們應該問的問題。
Everyone here is one of the best.
這裡的每個人都是最好的之一。
Who will they hire to ﻿teach us ?
他們會聘請誰來教我們？
The map is worth it.
這張地圖值得。
You're kidding.
開玩笑。
Hey guys.
大家好。
Come on like this.
就這樣來吧。
The one on me ...
我身上的那個...
That's not enough.
這還不夠。
I'll be back ﻿tomorrow with cash .
我明天會帶著現金回來。
Korkarım ki ...
科爾卡里姆基...
...rules are rules, Pete.
...規則就是規則，皮特。
Let's throw it out!
讓我們把它扔掉！
- Let's throw it out! - Are you serious?
- 讓我們把它扔掉！ - 你是認真的？
Let's throw it out!
讓我們把它扔掉！
It was good to see you, Pete.
很高興見到你，皮特。
Evet!
埃維特！
Thanks for the beers. Come back whenever you want.
謝謝你的啤酒。 隨時回來。
İrtifa 8.000.
伊爾蒂法 8.000。
I'm falling fast
我正在快速墜落
I can't reach the launch arm.
我夠不到發射臂。
Throw it! Throw it! Throw it!
丟它！ 丟它！ 丟它！
Goose! Dayan!
鵝！ 大雁！
He loved flying with you , Maverick.
他喜歡和你一起飛，特立獨行。
Dikkat!
迪卡特！
Günaydın.
居奈登。
Welcome to your ﻿special education continent.
歡迎來到您的特殊教育大陸。
Oturun.
奧圖倫。
This is Air Commander Admiral Bates.
這是空軍司令貝茨上將。
You're all Top Gun graduates.
你們都是壯志凌雲的畢業生。
You are elite pilots.
你們是精英飛行員。
You are the best of the best.
你是最好的。
These are yesterday.
這些是昨天。
The enemy's new 5th generation fighter jet has leveled the playing field.
敵人的新型第 5 代戰鬥機已經拉平了競爭環境。
Details are few, but now its technological advantage...
細節很少，但現在它的技術優勢......
... you can rest assured that we don't have it.
...您可以放心，我們沒有它。
Success is now more than ever...
現在的成功比以往任何時候都多……
... attached to a woman or a man ﻿inside a box .
... 附在盒子裡的女人或男人身上。
Half of you will pass the elimination.
你們中有一半人會通過淘汰賽。
One of you will be designated as the mission leader .
你們中的一個人將被指定為任務負責人。
The remaining half will remain as reinforcements.
剩下的一半將繼續作為增援。
Your instructor is also a Top Gun graduate.
你的教練也是壯志凌雲的畢業生。
He has real-world experience in ﻿every mission you are expected to master .
他在您期望掌握的每項任務中都有實際經驗。
Their achievements are legendary.
他們的成就堪稱傳奇。
He is widely regarded as one of ﻿the best pilots this program has produced .
他被廣泛認為是該計劃產生的最佳飛行員之一。
oh my god.
我的天啊。
What they teach you can make the difference between your death and your life.
他們教給你的東西可以使你的死亡和生命變得不同。
Introducing Captain Pete Mitchell.
介紹皮特·米切爾船長。
Lakabı, Maverick.
拉卡比，特立獨行。
Günaydın.
居奈登。
FAT guides.
脂肪指南。
It contains everything they want you to ﻿know about the program .
它包含他們希望您了解的有關該程序的所有信息。
I assume you know ﻿the contents of this book .
我假設你知道這本書的內容。
- That's right! - Yes, we know.
- 沒錯！ - 是的，我們知道。
Your enemy knows too.
你的敵人也知道。
Here we go.
開始了。
But what the enemy doesn't know...
但敵人不知道的是……
... your limits.
...你的極限。
I intend to find them.
我打算找到他們。
I want to test and force.
我想測試和強制。
Just what you know today..
就你今天所知道的..
... we'll start with your chests.
...我們將從你的胸部開始。
Show me what you can do.
告訴我你能做什麼。
Rooster?
公雞？
Bradley?
布拉德利？
Teğmen Bradshaw?
特門布拉德肖？
Yes, sir.
是的先生。
Let's leave this formality aside.
讓我們把這個形式放在一邊。
Are you going to kick me out of the team?
你要把我踢出隊伍嗎？
It's up to you, not me.
這取決於你，而不是我。
can i go
我可以去嗎
Good morning, Airmen. Your captain is speaking.
早安，飛行員。 你的船長在說話。
Welcome to basic flight maneuvers.
歡迎來到基本的飛行演習。
As reported, our exercise today is dogfighting.
據報導，我們今天的演習是鬥狗。
Guns only. No missiles.
只有槍。 沒有導彈。
We will not go below the 5,000 feet limit .
我們不會低於 5,000 英尺的限制。
You have to work as a team and shoot me or else...
你必須作為一個團隊工作並射擊我，否則......
Or what, sir?
或者什麼，先生？
Or I will shoot you.
否則我會射殺你。
If I shoot one of you, you both lose.
如果我向你們中的一個開槍，你們都會輸。
This guy's ego check
這傢伙的自我檢查
We'll handle it.
我們會處理的。
Let's make the game a little better, shall we?
讓我們把遊戲做得更好一點，好嗎？
- What's on your mind? - Whoever gets hit first should do 200 push-ups.
- 你在想什麼？  - 誰先被擊中應該做200個俯臥撑。
I don't like doing push-ups.
我不喜歡做俯臥撑。
They don't call it exercise for nothing, sir.
先生，他們不把它叫做鍛煉。
Agreed then, gentlemen.
那麼同意，先生們。
The fight has begun. Let's go to work.
戰鬥已經開始。 咱們上班去。
Fanboy, do you see it?
粉絲，你看到了嗎？
There's nothing ahead on the radar.
雷達上什麼都沒有。
It must be somewhere behind us.
它一定在我們身後的某個地方。
- It's bad! - Whoa!
- 這是壞的！ - 哇！
No more!
不再！
Ağır ol, Maverick.
Ağır ol，特立獨行。
Let's not get fired from day one.
我們不要從第一天就被解僱。
Charlie, down! Down! Maverick is coming!
查理，下來！ 下！ 小牛來了！
- Let's break up!
- 我們分手吧！
Hangman, where's your fireman?
劊子手，你的消防員呢？
- Rooster, where are you? - I've got your back, man.
- 公雞，你在哪裡？ - 我支持你，伙計。
I'm coming. Hold on, hold on!
我來了。 等一下，等一下！
Acele and, dostum! And Acele!
Acele 和，dostum！ 還有阿賽爾！
We have to leave!
我們必須離開！
do you see it?
你看到了嗎？
Rooster just saw the light, fellas.
公雞剛剛看到了光，伙計們。
And it cost him dearly.
這讓他付出了沉重的代價。
Not this time, old man.
這次不行，老鐵。
You cannot escape like this.
你不能像這樣逃跑。
damn it.
該死的。
Rooster, you're way down. You're under the limit!
公雞，你倒下了。 你低於極限！
Hassiktir!
哈西克提爾！
Öldün.
奧登。
Woe to your mother.
你媽媽有禍了。
189.
189.
That's how it is. 190...
就是這樣。  190...
We should have been there.
我們應該在那裡。
But we are not.
但我們不是。
And now you know something ﻿about the Rooster .
現在你對公雞有所了解。
We'll get another one when we get back , okay?
我們回來的時候再買一個，好嗎？
OK, pose.
好，擺姿勢。
- You're dead. - Damn!
- 你死了。 - 該死！
- You were shot. - Wow!
- 你被槍殺了。 - 哇！
Everything feels fun until you get hit .
在你被擊中之前，一切都感覺很有趣。
Phoenix, how about you tell everyone what Bob stands for?
菲尼克斯，你要不要告訴大家鮑勃代表什麼？
- No need to hide. - I'm in.
- 無需隱藏。 - 我在。
Don't get hooked, Bob.
不要上癮，鮑勃。
Wanna know why we call him Hangman ?
想知道我們為什麼叫他劊子手嗎？
Wait, wait, I found it. "Baby Sitting Here."
等等等等，我找到了。  “寶貝坐在這裡。”
Hassiktir lan!
哈西克提爾蘭！
Good morning, Airmen.
早安，飛行員。
The fight has begun.
戰鬥已經開始。
All right, Phoenix. Let's get this guy down.
好吧，鳳凰。 讓我們把這傢伙弄下來。
Arkanı kolla, Phoenix.
Arkanı kolla，鳳凰城。
- Right wing! - I'm breaking to the right!
- 右翼！ - 我向右突破！
- Where is this going? - That's why we call him Hangman.
- 這是要去哪裡？ - 這就是為什麼我們稱他為劊子手。
It always leaves you in the middle.
它總是把你留在中間。
It means leaving your ﻿burning man .
這意味著離開你的燃燒人。
A tactic I haven't seen in a ﻿long time .
很久沒見過的戰術了。
He called you a man, Phoenix. Will you accept this?
他稱你為男人，鳳凰。 你會接受這個嗎？
Unless he calls you a man.
除非他叫你男人。
- Where's Maverick, Bob? - God, his nose almost went in.
- 特立獨行的鮑勃在哪裡？ - 上帝，他的鼻子差點沒進去。
Get him after me, Hangman!
抓他，劊子手！
To the attention of our viewers at home.
引起國內觀眾的注意。
That's how fossils are buried.
化石就是這樣被埋葬的。
All right, Hangman. It's time to teach you a lesson.
好吧，劊子手。 是時候給你上一課了。
- You're dead, Phoenix. - Son of a bitch!
- 你死了，鳳凰。 - 王八蛋！
Let's go, Mav! Let's see what you got!
走吧，馬夫！ 讓我們看看你得到了什麼！
Come on!
來吧！
You'll be done soon. Hangman is coming.
你很快就會完成。 劊子手來了
Yes, we will see it.
是的，我們會看到的。
It's sensitive. Phoenix can't see it. How close am I?
它很敏感。 鳳凰看不到。 我離我有多近？
- Phoenix? - I'm dead, dickhead.
- 鳳凰？ - 我死了，白痴。
See you in the afterlife, Bagman.
巴格曼，來世見。
Where is this? Where?
這是哪裡？ 在哪裡？
Öldün.
奧登。
79!
79！
Yere! 80!
耶！  80！
All right, who's next?
好吧，下一個是誰？
- I shot you, Omaha. - Damn!
- 我開槍了，奧馬哈。 - 該死！
Vuruldun, Coyote.
Vuruldun，土狼。
This must be a joke.
這一定是個笑話。
Yere! 71!
耶！  71！
Yere! 72!
耶！  72！
Rooster, can I ask you a personal question?
公雞，我可以問你一個私人問題嗎？
If I say you can't ask, won't you ask?
如果我說你不能問，你不會問嗎？
What's your story with Maverick?
你和 Maverick 的故事是什麼？
It seems like it got you a little nervous .
好像讓你有點緊張。
- It's none of your business. - Where is this man?
- 這不關你的事。 - 這個人在哪裡？
I was always here.
我一直都在這裡。
Hassiktir be...
哈西克提爾...
Do you see now?
你現在看到了嗎？
Come on, let's finish this thing.
來吧，讓我們完成這件事。
The fight has begun!
戰鬥開始了！
What's wrong with these two?
這兩個有什麼問題？
Well, you got us here.
好吧，你把我們帶到了這裡。
How will you remove yourself?
你將如何移除自己？
You can quit whenever you want!
您可以隨時退出！
- How long do you want to continue, Rooster? - I can do as much as you, sir.
- 你想繼續多久，公雞？ - 先生，我能做的和你一樣多。
And that's enough for me.
這對我來說已經足夠了。
The past is past . for both of us.
過去就是過去。 為了我們倆。
You want to believe that , right?
你願意相信，對吧？
You go below the limit. Your space is running low!
你低於極限。 您的空間即將用盡！
If you want to see us both on the ground , so be it.
如果你想在地面上看到我們倆，那就這樣吧。
altitude! Altitude!
高度！ 高度！
Rise, rise!
起來，起來！
That's how it is. Don't think, just do.
就是這樣。 不要想，只要做。
Come on, Rooster. You're on your back! Get down and take your shot!
來吧，公雞。 你在你的背上！ 下來，拍你的照片！
I'm so low!
我這麼低！
It's too late now. You missed your chance.
現在為時已晚。 你錯過了機會。
Öldün.
奧登。
Yere in.
進了。
damn it!
該死的！
It's the same Rooster.
這是同一隻公雞。
Go see Harlow ﻿for your push-ups .
去哈洛看看你的俯臥撑。
OK, that's enough.
好的，這就夠了。
Rooster, that's enough, man.
公雞，夠了，伙計。
Going below the limit ? Disobedience?
低於極限？ 不服從？
- Trying to get fired? - Don't worry about it.
- 試圖被解僱？ - 不用擔心。
Bak...
巴...
I'm going on this mission.
我正在執行這個任務。
But if you get fired, you leave us to fly Hangman.
但是如果你被解雇了，你就讓我們去飛劊子手。
Talk to me! What was it?
跟我說話！ 它以前如何？
He took out my papers.
他拿出我的文件。
Ne? Kim?
氖？ 金?
Maverick.
特立獨行。
He took out my application and sent it back.
他拿出我的申請，然後寄回去。
It pushed me back four years.
它讓我倒退了四年。
Why would you do this?
你為什麼要這樣做？
The limit is 5000 feet above the ground.
限制是距離地面 5000 英尺。
This limit is not just for the safety of the pilots...
這個限制不僅僅是為了飛行員的安全......
... determined for the safety of ﻿aircraft as well .
... 也為飛機的安全而決心。
5000 feet is not an ordinary rule, it is a law.
5000英尺不是一般的規則，而是規律。
It must be obeyed like the law of gravity!
它必須像萬有引力定律一樣被遵守！
The limit for the mission will be much lower, sir.
任務的限制會低得多，長官。
And it cannot be changed without my consent !
未經我同意不能更改！
Especially in the middle of a workout.
尤其是在鍛煉的中間。
And that cobra maneuver?
那眼鏡蛇機動呢？
He could have killed all three of you.
他本可以殺了你們三個。
I never want to see ﻿this bullshit again.
我再也不想看到這種廢話了。
What exactly did you think you were teaching, Captain?
你到底認為你在教什麼，船長？
No matter how good they are, they still have something to learn, sir.
長官，無論他們多麼優秀，他們仍然有一些東西要學。
You're talking about the best fighter-plane pilots on the planet, Captain.
你說的是這個星球上最好的戰鬥機飛行員，船長。
And their careers that will end with them.
他們的職業生涯將與他們一起結束。
They will drop bombs from high altitude with little or no dogfight.
他們會從高空投下炸彈，很少或根本沒有混戰。
The parameters of this mission require things for which they were never prepared.
這項任務的參數需要他們從未準備過的東西。
To fight as a team and to a goal...
作為一個團隊並為一個目標而戰......
...to teach how to attack...
...教如何攻擊...
... you have less than three weeks.
...你只有不到三週的時間。
And for their safe return home.
並為了他們安全回家。
They'll be back home safely , sir.
他們會安全回家的，先生。
Every mission has risks.
每個任務都有風險。
These pilots accept that.
這些飛行員接受了這一點。
I don't, sir.
我不知道，先生。
Starting today, you will give us your training plans in writing ﻿every morning .
從今天開始，您將每天早上以書面形式向我們提供您的培訓計劃。
And nothing will be changed ﻿without my written consent .
未經我的書面同意，任何事情都不會改變。
- Including the limit, sir? - Especially the limit, Captain.
- 包括限額，先生？ - 特別是極限，船長。
Efendim.
埃芬迪姆。
What is this?
這是什麼？
Request to lower the limit, sir.
請求降低限制，先生。
For low altitude bomb drill in ﻿mission parameters .
用於任務參數中的低空炸彈演習。
You better learn a few things about timing , Captain.
你最好學習一些關於時間的東西，船長。
Hey, Coyote.
嘿，小狼。
Take a look at this.
看看這個。
The man is a legend. It's over there.
這個人是一個傳奇。 它在那邊。
No, no. next to it.
不，不。 在它的旁邊。
Is it familiar?
是不是很熟悉？
What is it here?
這是什麼？
Bradshaw.
布拉德肖。
It's like a living tomb.
它就像一個活的墳墓。
Hey, Theo.
嘿，提奧。
- But you've grown. - Hey, Mav.
- 但你已經長大了。 - 嘿，馬夫。
- Emilia? - I know. I've grown a lot.
- 艾米莉亞？ - 我知道。 我成長了很多。
Evet.
埃特。
If you want a drink, get it yourself.
如果你想喝一杯，自己去拿。
No, I stopped by to pay my debt.
不，我停下來償還我的債務。
Anne!
安妮！
- Hey, how's your dad? - He's in Hawaii with his wife.
- 嘿，你爸爸好嗎？ - 他和他的妻子在夏威夷。
Anne!
安妮！
Mav says he brought your money.
馬夫說他帶來了你的錢。
Never mind.
沒關係。
I insist.
我堅持。
Thank you, Captain.
謝謝你，船長。
Say your account is closed.
假設您的帳戶已關閉。
Captain? still?
隊長？ 仍然？
A Captain with many medals.
擁有許多勳章的船長。
Finish it. We have to get the boat repaired.
完成它。 我們必須把船修好。
- I can't come. - What do you mean you can't come?
- 我不能來。 - 你不能來是什麼意思？
There is a test tomorrow. I need to work.
明天有考試。 我需要工作。
They reported today.
他們今天報導了。
I can't take him alone.
我不能單獨帶他。
You use the engine.
你使用引擎。
Why are we taking it for repair?
我們為什麼要把它拿去修理？
- To get the engine repaired.
- 修理髮動機。
I can help.
我可以搭把手。
We don't always stand by like this.
我們並不總是這樣袖手旁觀。
Yapma ya?
亞普瑪是嗎？
According to the wind direction..
根據風向..
- ﻿...we set sail. - OK.
- ﻿...我們啟航了。 - 好的。
What does this mean?
這是什麼意思？
And you'll be in my navy!
你將在我的海軍中！
I'm not driving, Penny.
我不開車，佩妮。
I'm landing on them.
我降落在他們身上。
No more difficult than steering an airplane.
並不比駕駛飛機更難。
How will I do it?
我將如何做？
Pulling the green rope over there.
把那根綠繩拉過去。
Yeşil halat ...
耶希爾哈拉特...
Yes, pull hard!
是的，用力拉！
Uradaki kola sar!
浦崎可樂！
He will open the mainsail!
他將打開主帆！
- Flip, with all your might! - OK!
- 翻轉，全力以赴！ - 好的！
Güzel.
古澤爾。
Şimdi...
辛迪...
are you ready?
你準備好了嗎？
Neye?
尼耶？
Additional speed.
額外的速度。
Now you're from the Navy.
現在你來自海軍。
Thanks for ﻿helping out on the boat .
感謝您在船上幫忙。
I 'm not sure I'm helping.
我不確定我在幫忙。
Don't give me that look.
不要給我那種眼神。
Which look?
哪個樣子？
that's it.
這就對了。
Good night, Pete.
晚安，皮特。
Good night, Penny.
晚安，佩妮。
Time is your worst enemy.
時間是你最大的敵人。
Stage 1 of the mission is to advance at low altitude in two teams.
任務的第一階段是兩隊低空推進。
You will reach your destination through this narrow canyon.
您將通過這個狹窄的峽谷到達目的地。
The area smells of radar-mounted heat -seeking missiles.
該地區散發著安裝在雷達上的熱追踪導彈的氣味。
These missiles are deadly.
這些導彈是致命的。
But they are designed to protect the sky above , not the canyon below.
但它們旨在保護上方的天空，而不是下方的峽谷。
Because the enemy knows that no one is crazy enough to fly under them.
因為敵人知道沒有人瘋狂到可以在他們下面飛翔。
That's exactly what I'm going to train you for.
這正是我要訓練你的目的。
On mission day, your altitude will be 1000 feet.
在任務日，您的海拔高度將是 1000 英尺。
Maksimum.
馬克西姆。
If you pass this altitude, the radar will catch you...
如果你經過這個高度，雷達會捕捉到你……
...and you die.
……你死了。
Your speed will be 660 knots.
你的速度將是 660 節。
Minimum.
最低限度。
Arrival time at destination 2.5 minutes.
到達目的地時間2.5分鐘。
This is because of the 5th generation warplanes waiting at the ﻿nearby airport .
這是因為第五代戰機在附近機場等候。
If you encounter ﻿these planes in an F-18 ...
如果您在 F-18 中遇到這些飛機...
... you will die.
... 你會死。
So before these planes even have a chance to catch you...
所以在這些飛機甚至有機會抓住你之前......
... you must enter, hit your target and disappear.
...您必須進入，擊中目標並消失。
This makes time your biggest competitor.
這讓時間成為你最大的競爭對手。
Your navigation system has a simulation of the canyon.
您的導航系統模擬了峽谷。
The faster you cross ﻿this canyon ...
你越過這個峽谷的速度越快......
... the more difficult it will be for you to stay ﻿under the radar and stay away from enemy planes .
......你越難躲在雷達下並遠離敵機。
As the turns get harder , the force of gravity on your body increases exponentially.
隨著轉彎變得越來越難，你身體上的重力成倍增加。
It compresses your lungs...
它壓縮你的肺...
It forces the blood in your brain to flow...
它迫使你大腦中的血液流動......
It affects your decisions and reaction time.
它會影響您的決策和反應時間。
They asked me not to overload you.
他們要求我不要讓你超負荷。
So your altitude is 1,300 feet and your time to destination is 3 minutes.
因此，您的海拔高度為 1,300 英尺，到達目的地的時間為 3 分鐘。
Good luck.
祝你好運。
Dostum...
杜斯塔姆...
We are 1.30 minutes away from the destination. We're two seconds behind.
我們距離目的地有 1.30 分鐘的路程。 我們落後了兩秒。
We must increase our speed by 80 knots.
我們必須將速度提高 80 節。
Hızlanmalıyız, Coyote.
Hızlanmalıyız，土狼。
Got it, I'm increasing the speed.
明白了，我正在加快速度。
Hassiktir!
哈西克提爾！
- Why did they die? - We've crossed the 300-foot limit.
- 他們為什麼死了？  - 我們已經越過了 300 英尺的限制。
And the missiles took us down.
導彈把我們擊落了。
- No. Why did they die? - I slowed down and didn't give him a warning.
- 不。他們為什麼死了？ - 我放慢了速度，沒有給他警告。
- It was my fault. - For not communicating with your team.
- 是我的錯。 - 不與您的團隊溝通。
- I'm sorry, sir... - Will their families accept this at their funeral?
- 對不起，先生... - 他們的家人會在葬禮上接受這個嗎？
No, sir.
不，先生。
Why didn't you anticipate the return? You were informed in training.
為什麼你沒有預料到回報？ 你在訓練中被告知。
Don't tell me.
不要告訴我。
Tell his family.
告訴他的家人。
Hangman, be heavy! The canyon narrows.
劊子手，重一點！ 峽谷變窄了。
No problem, Payback. Increase your speed.
沒問題，回報。 提高你的速度。
You're going too fast, man!
你走得太快了，伙計！
It wouldn't hurt to arrive first.
最先到達也無妨。
Damn, slow down
媽的，慢點
I can't stay on course!
我不能堅持下去！
There's a wall in front of you! Attention, attention, attention!
你面前有一堵牆！ 注意，注意，注意！
- What happened? - I flew as fast as I could.
- 發生了什麼？ - 我盡可能快地飛。
As if my life depended on it.
好像我的生命依賴於它。
And he put his team in danger and your yandere is dead.
他讓他的團隊處於危險之中，你的yandere已經死了。
They couldn't reach me.
他們無法聯繫到我。
Rooster! We're 20 seconds behind and it's increasing!
公雞！ 我們落後了 20 秒，而且還在增加！
we are fine! Maintain your speed.
我們都很好！ 保持你的速度。
We're going 500 nautical miles.
我們要去500海裡。
Just keep your speed.
只要保持你的速度。
Rooster, we're running late!
公雞，我們要遲到了！
We're alive though. We'll make up for it later .
雖然我們還活著。 我們稍後會彌補。
Başaramayacağız!
巴薩拉馬亞卡格茲！
Listen to me! Maintain your speed.
聽我說！ 保持你的速度。
Başarabiliriz.
巴拉比利里斯。
Why did you die?
你為什麼死？
You are the team leader above.
你是上面的團隊負責人。
Why did you and your team die
為什麼你和你的團隊死了
Sir, he was the only one to reach the target.
長官，他是唯一一個達到目標的人。
One minute late.
遲到一分鐘。
He gave the ﻿enemy planes time to land him .
他讓敵機有時間讓他降落。
- He's dead. - You can't know that.
- 他死了。 - 你不能知道。
You're not flying fast enough.
你飛得不夠快。
We don't have a second to waste.
我們沒有一秒鐘可以浪費。
- We've reached the goal. - And superior enemy planes...
- 我們已經達到了目標。 - 和優越的敵機......
... cut you off while you were leaving.
...在你離開時切斷你的電話。
- Then it's a dogfight. - Against 5th generation warplanes.
- 然後是一場混戰。 - 對抗第五代戰機。
Yes, we still have a chance.
是的，我們還有機會。
- In an F-18. - It's not on the plane, sir.
- 在 F-18 中。  - 它不在飛機上，先生。
- It's on the pilot. - Exactly!
- 它在飛行員身上。 - 確切地！
There is more than one way to ﻿fly in this mission .
在這個任務中飛行的方式不止一種。
You really don't understand.
你真的不明白。
In this mission a man either flies like a Maverick...
在這個任務中，一個人要么像小牛一樣飛翔......
...or he can't come back.
……不然他就回不來了。
There is no resentment to be offended.
沒有怨恨被冒犯。
But you still succeed every time.
但你仍然每次都能成功。
You better listen to the ﻿criticisms a little bit .
你最好聽聽批評。
That's all. Lieutenant...
就這些。 中尉...
We're going to war, son.
我們要去打仗了，兒子。
The kind that no living pilot has ever seen.
沒有在世飛行員見過的那種。
Onun bile.
奧農膽汁。
Now is not the time to ﻿think about the past .
現在不是考慮過去的時候。
- What does that mean now? - Rooster.
- 現在是什麼意思？ - 公雞。
I can't be the only one who knows that ﻿Maverick flew with his father .
我不可能是唯一一個知道小牛和他父親一起飛的人。
- That's enough. - And while Maverick was flying with his father...
- 足夠了。 - 當小牛和他的父親一起飛行時......
Hey! Hey!
嘿！ 嘿！
For sure! Enough!
當然！ 足夠的！
- Son of a bitch! - Hey, come on!
- 王八蛋！ - 嘿，快點！
No hassle. I am fine.
沒有麻煩。 我沒事。
- That's enough. - He's not fit for the job.
- 足夠了。 - 他不適合這份工作。
- Enough! - You know this.
- 足夠的！ - 你知道這個。
You know him, don't you?
你認識他，不是嗎？
You can all disperse.
你們都可以散了。
We need to meet.
我們需要見面。
It's not a good time.
這不是一個好時機。
I'm not asking.
我不是在問。
Maverick.
特立獨行。
It's gotten worse.
它變得更糟。
Nobody knows.
沒人知道。
There is nothing else I can do.
我無能為力。
It hurts ﻿even when talking .
即使在說話時也很痛。
Sarah, I'm so sorry.
莎拉，我很抱歉。
Amiral.
上將。
Here is my burner.
這是我的燃燒器。
I want to talk about business.
我想談談生意。
Please don't worry about me.
請不要擔心我。
what can i do for you
我能為你做什麼
I want to talk about work.
我想談談工作。
Peki.
佩奇。
Rooster is still mad at me for what I did.
公雞仍然因為我的所作所為而生我的氣。
I thought you'd ﻿understand why .
我以為你會明白為什麼。
I hope he forgives me.
我希望他能原諒我。
There is still time.
還有時間。
Less than three weeks to the task .
不到三週就到了任務。
The child is not ready.
孩子還沒準備好。
So teach him.
所以教他。
It's not about what I can give him.
這不是我能給他什麼。
Ice, please.
冰，請。
Don't ask me to send ﻿another person to die , please.
請不要讓我派另一個人去死。
Don't ask me to send it.
不要要求我發送它。
send me
給我
It's time to quit.
是時候放棄了。
I don't know how.
我不知道怎麼。
I'm not a teacher, Ice.
我不是老師，冰。
I am a fighter jet pilot.
我是一名戰鬥機飛行員。
The Navy wants me to train.
海軍要我訓練。
I'm not this.
我不是這個。
This is my personality.
這是我的個性。
How can I teach this?
我怎麼能教這個？
Even if I could teach, that's not what Rooster wants.
即使我可以教書，那也不是公雞想要的。
That's not what the Navy wants.
這不是海軍想要的。
That's why they came to me last time.
這就是他們上次來找我的原因。
You 're the only reason ﻿I'm here .
你是我在這裡的唯一原因。
If I send him on this mission...
如果我派他去執行這個任務...
... he may never return home.
...他可能永遠不會回家。
And if I don't send him...
如果我不送他...
... will never forgive me.
……永遠不會原諒我。
Either way, I will lose him forever.
不管怎樣，我會永遠失去他。
It's time to quit.
是時候放棄了。
Biliyorum.
膽汁。
Biliyorum...
膽...
The Navy needs the Maverick.
海軍需要小牛。
The boy needs Maverick.
男孩需要特立獨行。
That's why I vouched for you.
這就是我為你擔保的原因。
That's why you're still here.
這就是為什麼你還在這裡。
Teşekkürler, Ice.
Teşekkürler，冰。
for everything.
一切。
One last thing.
最後一件事。
Which of us was the better pilot? You or me?
我們誰是更好的飛行員？ 你或我？
Let's not ruin this beautiful moment.
讓我們不要破壞這個美好的時刻。
Come on, here we go!
來吧，我們開始吧！
- Sir? - What is this?
- 先生？ - 這是什麼？
Dogfight football.
格鬥足球。
Attack and defense at the same time.
攻擊和防禦同時進行。
Who is winning?
誰贏了？
I guess they stopped keeping score a long time ago.
我猜他們很久以前就停止記分了。
The team still has a week of practice, Captain.
小隊還有一周的訓練時間，隊長。
- Every minute counts. - Yes sir.
- 每一分鐘都很重要。 - 是的先生。
So why are we playing games here?
那我們為什麼要在這裡玩遊戲呢？
You told me to form a team , sir.
先生，您讓我組隊。
Here is your team.
這是你的團隊。
Should I go before Emilia returns?
我應該在艾米莉亞回來之前去嗎？
He's staying with his friend tonight.
他今晚和他的朋友住在一起。
You and Emilia are much more...
你和艾米莉亞更...
...you seem close... compared to the last time I saw it.
......你看起來很接近......與我上次看到它相比。
Yes. We are.
是的。 我們是。
Şey...
餵...
He wanted more freedom than ﻿I thought he was ready for .
他想要的自由比我想像的要多。
Who did he get this from?
他從誰那裡得到這個？
That I should trust him...
我應該相信他...
... I finally realized it.
……我終於意識到了。
I have to let ﻿him make his own mistakes every now and then.
我不得不讓他時不時地犯下自己的錯誤。
It's not an easy choice.
這不是一個容易的選擇。
Is that what happened with the Rooster?
公雞是這樣的嗎？
I pulled out your paperwork from ﻿the Naval Academy .
我從海軍學院拿出你的文件。
I stole years from your career.
我從你的職業生涯中偷走了幾年。
Neden?
內登？
After what happened to Goose, I couldn't let him fly.
在鵝發生了什麼事之後，我不能讓他飛。
He made me promise before he died.
他死前向我保證。
Does Rooster know this?
公雞知道嗎？
He will always hate me ﻿for what I did .
他會因為我所做的一切而永遠恨我。
Why would I send it then?
那我為什麼要寄呢？
It's not an easy choice.
這不是一個容易的選擇。
I was trying to be the ﻿father he lost .
我試圖成為他失去的父親。
Sadece...
薩迪斯...
I wish I had done it differently.
我希望我做得不一樣。
The truth is...
事實是...
I didn't think you were ready.
我沒想到你已經準備好了。
Is it ready now?
現在準備好了嗎？
Mom, I'm here!
媽媽，我來了！
You were supposed to stay in Caron tonight ?
你今晚應該留在卡倫嗎？
Caron was going somewhere with her family!
Caron 和她的家人要去某個地方！
- I'd better go. - You better go.
- 我最好去。 - 你最好走。
Did you eat?
你吃了沒？
No, it's okay. I 'll prepare something for you.
不，沒關係。 我會為你準備一些東西。
I'm getting off right now!
我馬上下車！
wait! Not from there.
等待！ 不是從那裡。
Look, I need to be an example.
看，我需要成為一個例子。
I can't be the woman who brings a ﻿man home on a first date .
我不能成為第一次約會就帶男人回家的女人。
This is not our first date!
這不是我們的第一次約會！
You know what I mean.
你知道我的意思。
Pekala.
佩卡拉。
OK. But I'm getting out of the window for the last time, just so you know.
好的。 但我是最後一次走出窗外，你知道的。
- We'll see. - No.
- 走著瞧。 - 不。
No, I'm serious.
不，我是認真的。
I will not leave you again.
我不會再離開你了。
Shut up!
住口！
Come on, get out of here!
來吧，離開這裡！
Is he still nagging?
他還在嘮叨嗎？
Günaydın.
居奈登。
Your target is the uranium enrichment plant...
你的目標是鈾濃縮廠...
... will start working sooner than expected.
...將比預期更快開始工作。
The raw uranium will be delivered to the plant in 10 days.
原鈾將在 10 天內運抵工廠。
As a result, your mission has been pushed forward a week.
結果，你的任務被推進了一周。
To avoid contaminating ﻿the target valley with radiation .
避免輻射污染目標山谷。
Sir, no one here has successfully completed the low-altitude course.
先生，這裡沒有人成功完成低空課程。
Yet you have been ordered to advance.
然而，你已被命令前進。
Yüzbaşı.
尤茲巴什。
2. We have one week to focus on Phase .
2. 我們有一周的時間專注於階段。
The most dangerous part of the mission.
任務中最危險的部分。
A hard dive that required ﻿two miracles in a row, and...
一次艱難的潛水，需要連續創造兩個奇蹟，並且...
... to leave the package.
...離開包裹。
Two pairs of F- 18s will advance to the target, maintaining their attack pattern.
兩對 F-18 將向目標前進，保持它們的攻擊模式。
In order for the mission to succeed and for you to survive...
為了任務的成功和你的生存......
... it is very important ﻿that these planes work in coordination and as a team.
......非常重要的是這些飛機必須協調並作為一個團隊工作。
As you know, the facility is between two mountains.
如您所知，該設施位於兩座山之間。
In the last step, you will go straight into a hard dive.
在最後一步中，您將直接進入艱苦的潛水。
This gives you the opportunity to maintain the lowest possible altitude and...
這使您有機會保持盡可能低的高度並...
...will recognize a single angle of attack.
...將識別單一的攻擊角度。
Your target is in an area of ﻿​​less than 3 meters .
你的目標在小於 3 米的範圍內。
The first two aircraft will paint the target with a laser sight.
前兩架飛機將用激光瞄準器為目標上色。
The first pair is placed in an exposed vent...
第一對放置在暴露的通風口中......
... will drop a laser-guided bomb and hit the reactor.
... 將投下激光制導炸彈並擊中反應堆。
This will leave an open space ﻿for the second couple .
這將為第二對夫婦留下一個開放空間。
This was the first miracle.
這是第一個奇蹟。
The second team will deliver the killing blow.
第二隊將提供致命一擊。
And it will destroy the target.
它會摧毀目標。
This is the second miracle.
這是第二個奇蹟。
If either team misses the target...
如果任何一支球隊都錯過了目標......
- I missed! - Mission fails.
- 我錯過了！ - 任務失敗。
damn it.
該死的。
You will have to make a hard ascent to avoid hitting the mountain.
您將不得不艱難攀登以避免撞到山上。
You'd eat at least 8 Gs on ﻿that steep ascent at that speed .
以那種速度陡峭的上升，你至少會吃掉 8 Gs。
9. Minimum.
9. 最低限度。
The fuselage of the F-18s is designed for 7.5 G.
F-18 的機身設計為 7.5 G。
That's the accepted limit.
這是可接受的限制。
You will endure more ﻿to survive this mission .
你會忍受更多的 ﻿來完成這個任務。
Even if it means ﻿twisting your torso .
即使這意味著扭曲你的軀幹。
Your heartbeat will accelerate and you will feel pressure close to 4 tons.
你的心跳會加速，你會感覺到接近 4 噸的壓力。
Your skull will crush your spine.
你的頭骨會壓碎你的脊椎。
Your lungs will explode as ﻿if an elephant is sitting on your chest .
你的肺會爆炸，就像一頭大象坐在你的胸前一樣。
You will fight with ﻿all your might just not to faint.
您將竭盡全力不暈倒。
And right here you will be the most vulnerable.
在這裡，您將是最脆弱的。
This is... the coffin corner.
這是……棺材角。
Assuming you avoid ﻿hitting this mountain ...
假設你避免撞到這座山......
... you will go straight into enemy radar and you will lose your privacy.
...您將直接進入敵人的雷達，您將失去隱私。
Within seconds, enemy missiles will be fired at you.
幾秒鐘內，敵人的導彈就會向你發射。
You've all had a malfunction in the air before...
你們之前都曾在空中發生過故障……
...but this will bring you to the point of destroying ﻿both you and your plane .
...但這會讓你達到摧毀你和你的飛機的地步。
Sir, can this task be accomplished?
先生，這個任務能完成嗎？
The answer to this question is...
這個問題的答案是……
Depends on the pilot in the box.
取決於盒子裡的飛行員。
- Talk to me, Bob. - We're 12 seconds late to the destination.
- 跟我說話，鮑勃。 - 我們比目的地晚了 12 秒。
- We have to speed up. We must speed up. - Fuck it.
- 我們必須加快速度。 我們必須加快速度。 - 去他媽的。
Got it. Try to stay with me .
知道了。 試著留在我身邊。
Who is this?
這是誰？
Blue Team, your place has been determined.
藍隊，你的位置已經確定了。
- Fuck it, it's Maverick. - What is he doing here?
- 去他的，這是特立獨行的。 - 他在這裡做什麼？
I am an enemy plane ﻿coming to intercept you.
我是來攔截你的敵機。
Blue Team, what will you do?
藍隊，你會怎麼做？
20 km. away, in the direction of 10. It's not too close.
20 公里。 遠，在10的方向。也不是太近。
You have the word. What would you like to do?
你有這個詞。 你想幹什麼？
We continue. We're close.
我們繼續。 我們很親密。
Hedefte kal
赫德夫特卡爾轉向北方
- Prepare for ascension. - Stand by at the laser, Bob.
- 準備提升。 - 在激光旁待命，鮑勃。
Got it, I'm waiting.
知道了，我在等
Blue Team, the enemy is still approaching.
藍隊，敵人還在逼近。
I'm rising now!
我現在正在崛起！
Congratulations, Bob! Maverick down?
祝賀你，鮑勃！ 小牛倒閉？
10 km. away, coming fast!
10 公里。 走，快來！
In the target field of view.
在目標視野中。
Where's my laser, Bob?
我的激光在哪裡，鮑勃？
Does not lock, does not lock!
不鎖不鎖！
It doesn't work. Sorry, I can't lock it!
它不起作用。 對不起，我不能鎖！
So I'm shooting blind!
所以我在瞎拍！
Damn, I missed!
媽的，我錯過了！
- I shot you. - Leave me alone, brothers.
- 我開槍打死你。 - 放開我，兄弟們。
It's silly, we're dead.
太傻了，我們死定了。
Blue Team, you failed.
藍隊，你失敗了。
Balance your wings, Coyote.
平衡你的翅膀，土狼。
Coyote, balance your wings!
郊狼，平衡你的翅膀！
Coyote, answer!
土撥鼠，回答！
He's sick, he's unconscious.
他病了，他昏迷了。
Coyote?!
土狼？！
Çakılacak!
恰克拉克！
I'm chasing after you!
我在追你！
Hadi, his ver bana! Its worms!
哈迪，他的名字！ 它的蠕蟲！
Get rid of it, Coyote.
擺脫它，土狼。
Until, Coyote. Until, until!
直到，郊狼。 直到，直到！
Cevap ver, Coyote!
Cevap ver，土狼！
Coyote! Coyote!
郊狼！ 郊狼！
Coyote, are you okay?
小狼，你還好嗎？
İyiyim.
伊伊伊姆。
Beautiful, beautiful.
漂亮漂亮。
Enough for today.
今天到此為止。
This was close.
這很接近。
He was too close.
他離得太近了。
flock of birds! Herd of birds
鳥群！ 鳥群
A flock of birds?
一群鳥？
Phoenix, right engine on fire!
鳳凰城，右引擎著火了！
Yükseliyorum!
尤克斯利約魯姆！
I'm speeding.
我在超速。
I turn off the fuel on the right engine.
我關閉了右側發動機的燃油。
I'm putting out the fire.
我正在滅火。
- Right engine stalled. - It's still spinning.
- 右發動機熄火。 - 它還在旋轉。
I'm trying to reboot.
我正在嘗試重新啟動。
Your tail is on fire! Make a sharp turn!
你的尾巴著火了！ 急轉彎！
Hızlanıyorum.
希茲拉尼約魯姆。
damn it.
該死的。
We are burning. We're on fire!
我們在燃燒。 我們著火了！
- Damn it! - Fire in the engine.
- 該死的！ - 發動機著火。
I'm extinguishing both engines!
我正在熄滅兩個引擎！
Phoenix, Bob! Jump, jump!
鳳凰，鮑勃！ 跳，跳！
There are malfunctions everywhere! All values ​​are dropping!
到處都是故障！ 所有的價值都在下降！
- System malfunction. - I can't control it.
- 系統故障。 - 我無法控制它。
We're falling, Phoenix? We're falling!
我們正在墜落，鳳凰？ 我們正在墜落！
You have no other chance! Throw it! Throw it!
你沒有其他機會了！ 丟它！ 丟它！
They will watch them for a while longer.
他們會再看一會兒。
But they will be fine.
但他們會沒事的。
Kaybettik.
凱貝提克。
I almost lost my burner too.
我也差點丟了燃燒器。
Şanslısın.
Şanslısın。
For making it to the last round.
為了進入最後一輪。
There will be others.
還會有其他人。
It's easy for you to say.
你說起來很容易。
You don't have a wife...
你沒有老婆……
You have no children...
你沒有孩子...
There's no one to mourn when you crash .
當你崩潰時，沒有人可以哀悼。
Evine git.
伊万·吉特。
Let's get some sleep.
讓我們睡一覺吧。
Why did you take out my papers ﻿at the academy ?
你為什麼在學院拿出我的論文？
Why did you get in my way?!
你為什麼擋著我的路？！
You were not ready.
你還沒有準備好。
What was I not ready for?
我沒有準備好做什麼？
- To fly like you? - No.
- 像你一樣飛翔？ - 不。
Don't forget the book. To trust your instincts.
不要忘記這本書。 相信你的直覺。
Not thinking, just doing.
不思考，只做。
If you start thinking above, you will die.
如果你開始想上面，你會死。
Believe me.
相信我。
My father believed in you too.
我父親也相信你。
I will not make the same mistake.
我不會犯同樣的錯誤。
Maverick.
特立獨行。
Ready, aim, fire!
準備瞄准開火！
It's impossible for me to understand ﻿what you're feeling right now .
我無法理解你現在的感受。
Take some time off. whatever you need.
休息一段時間。 隨便你想要什麼。
Thank you sir , but there is no time. Task...
謝謝大佬，可是沒時間了。 任務...
I'm taking over the authority here.
我正在接管這裡的權力。
Efendim?
埃芬迪姆？
- We both know you don't want this job. - Sir, they're not ready.
- 我們都知道你不想要這份工作。 - 先生，他們還沒準備好。
It was your job to prepare them.
準備它們是你的工作。
They must believe that ﻿this mission can succeed .
他們必須相信，這項使命一定能成功。
But you failed to do so.
但你沒有這樣做。
- Sir... - You're grounded, Captain.
- 先生... - 你被禁足了，船長。
permanently.
永久。
- Sir... - That's it.
- 先生... - 就是這樣。
Duydum.
杜杜姆。
Üzgünüm.
烏茲古努姆。
What will you do?
你會怎麼做？
Ice is no more.
冰沒有了。
What other choice do I have?
我還有什麼選擇？
You have to find a way back yourself .
你必須自己想辦法回去。
Penny...
一分錢​​...
That's it from me.
這就是我的。
This is over.
一切都結束了。
Pete, even if you lost your firefight in mid-air...
皮特，即使你在半空中失去了交火......
You keep fighting.
你繼續戰鬥。
You just don't give up.
你只是不放棄。
They are your pilots.
他們是你的飛行員。
If anything happens to them...
如果他們有什麼事...
... you can never forgive yourself.
……你永遠無法原諒自己。
I don't know what to do.
我不知道該怎麼辦。
But you will find a way.
但是你會找到方法的。
I know you.
我認識你。
Captain Mitchell is no longer your instructor.
米切爾船長不再是你的導師。
Your new mission parameters ﻿as of today .
您今天的新任務參數。
Destination time is now 4 minutes.
目的地時間現在是 4 分鐘。
You will enter the valley level by Reducing your speed.
您將通過降低速度進入山谷級別。
You shall not exceed ﻿420 nautical miles .
不得超過﻿420海裡。
Sir, don't we give their planes time to spot us?
長官，我們不給他們的飛機時間來發現我們嗎？
You have a chance to get off the plane, Lieutenant.
你有機會下飛機，中尉。
What are your chances of surviving ﻿hitting the mountain vertically ?
你垂直撞山的機會有多大？
You will be attacking ﻿the target from higher altitude.
您將從更高的高度攻擊目標。
It's on the north wall.
它在北牆上。
Keeping your laser on target will be more difficult...
讓你的激光瞄準目標將更加困難......
...but you will avoid ﻿the steep climb .
...但你會避免陡峭的攀登。
And then the missiles will turn us to dust.
然後導彈會把我們變成塵土。
Who is this?
這是誰？
From Maverick to Field Control.
從特立獨行到現場控制。
I'm entering the Alpha Point. I want green zone approval.
我正在進入阿爾法點。 我想要綠區批准。
Maverick, this is Field Control...
特立獨行，這是現場控制...
Green zone confirmed but...
綠區已確認，但...
I don't see your name on the program , sir.
先生，我沒有在節目中看到您的名字。
It's not too late though.
不過現在還為時不晚。
Güzel.
古澤爾。
Arrival time at new destination 2 minutes 15 seconds.
到達新目的地的時間為 2 分 15 秒。
2.15 mi? This is impossible.
2.15 英里？ 這是不可能的。
I'm getting close to the first point. Maverick is on its way.
我正在接近第一點。 特立獨行正在路上。
Hassiktir.
哈西克提爾。
Hadi!
哈迪！
Tırmanıyorum. 3, 2, 1.
蒂爾馬尼約魯姆。  3、2、1。
Bombs are on their way.
炸彈正在路上。
Tam 12'den! Hassiktir!
譚12'den！ 哈西克提爾！
Evet.
埃特。
Woe to your mother.
你媽媽有禍了。
You put me in a difficult position , Captain.
你讓我陷入了困境，船長。
On the one hand, you showed that this mission can be flown.
一方面，你證明了這個任務是可以飛行的。
Maybe the only way to get out alive.
也許是活著出去的唯一方法。
On the other hand...
另一方面...
...by smuggling a multimillion-dollar military property and never again...
......通過走私價值數百萬美元的軍事財產，再也不會......
... you did it by using it in a way that it can't take off.
...您通過以無法起飛的方式使用它來做到這一點。
Iceman is no longer here to protect you.
冰人不再在這裡保護你。
It's up to me to take you to court-martial and...
由我決定帶你去軍事法庭...
... have everything needed to get ﻿kicked out of the army .
...擁有被趕出軍隊所需的一切。
What do you think I should do?
你覺得我應該怎麼做？
Should I risk the lives of my pilots, and perhaps the chances of success of this mission...
我是否應該拿我的飛行員的生命冒險，或許還有這個任務成功的機會……
...or else...
...要不然...
... as the leader of the faculty...
...作為教師的領導...
...and risk my career ?
...並冒險我的職業生涯？
- Sir... - I think the Admiral didn't want an answer to his question.
- 長官... - 我想海軍上將不想回答他的問題。
Anladım.
安拉迪姆。
Talk to me, Goose.
跟我說話，鵝。
Komutan Mitchell.
科穆坦·米切爾。
You are where you belong.
你是屬於你的地方。
make us proud.
讓我們感到自豪。
It was an honor to fly with you.
和你一起飛是一種榮幸。
Each of you represents the best of the best.
你們每個人都代表著最好的。
This is a very special mission.
這是一個非常特殊的使命。
My choices are only reflections of that.
我的選擇只是反映了這一點。
First Foxtrot team members.
第一個 Foxtrot 團隊成員。
Payback ve Fanboy.
回報 ve Fanboy。
Phoenix ve Bob.
菲尼克斯和鮑勃。
And your fire.
還有你的火。
Rooster.
公雞。
The rest of you are in support roles on board...
你們其餘的人在船上擔任支持角色...
... you will continue to stay.
...你會繼續留下來。
Dağılabilirsiniz.
達拉比利西尼茲。
Your target is a threat that needs ﻿immediate attention .
您的目標是需要立即關注的威脅。
It's a secret uranium enrichment plant out of surveillance.
這是一個不受監視的秘密鈾濃縮廠。
In an underground bunker. Between these two mountains.
在一個地下掩體中。 在這兩座山之間。
There are 5th class warplanes ﻿at a nearby airport in the region .
該地區附近的機場有五級戰機。
After ﻿you take off and cross the border ...
您起飛並過境後...
...from the USS Ladygulf to the enemy 's airfield here...
......從USS Ladygulf到這裡的敵人機場......
... synchronized Tomahawk missiles will be fired.
... 將發射同步的戰斧導彈。
This will put their tracks out of play.
這將使他們的曲目無法播放。
But you'll have to deal with planes that have already taken off.
但是您將不得不處理已經起飛的飛機。
As soon as those missiles land at the airport, they'll know you've arrived.
一旦這些導彈降落在機場，他們就會知道你已經到達。
Your arrival time at the destination will be 2 minutes and 30 seconds.
您到達目的地的時間為 2 分 30 秒。
If it takes longer than that, you'll be on the radar of hijacked planes by the ﻿Tomahawks .
如果花費的時間比這更長，您將在戰斧劫持飛機的雷達上。
You were trained for this.
你為此受過訓練。
Good luck back home.
祝你好運回家。
Show your days.
展示你的日子。
Efendim!
埃芬迪姆！
Ben...
本...
- I meant... - All personnel take their seats.
- 我是說... - 所有人員就座
All personnel take their places for departure.
全體人員各就各位出發。
Konuşuruz.
科努蘇魯茲。
Döndüğümüzde.
Döndüğümüzde。
Hey, Bradley? Bradley!
嘿，布拉德利？ 布拉德利！
Hey...
嘿...
You can do this.
你可以這樣做。
Maverick.
特立獨行。
Maverick?
特立獨行？
Hey, are you with me?
嘿，你和我在一起嗎？
Don't throw that look, man.
不要扔那種眼神，伙計。
I only have this look.
我只有這個樣子。
Thank you.
謝謝你。
If we don't see each other again...
如果我們再也見不到了……
It was my honor, Captain.
這是我的榮幸，船長。
Dagger-1. Ready for takeoff and standby.
匕首-1。 準備起飛和待命。
Dagger-Reinforcement pending.
匕首增援待定。
Dagger-4 is ready to take off.
Dagger-4 準備起飛。
Dagger-3 is ready to take off.
Dagger-3 準備起飛。
Dagger-2 is ready to take off.
Dagger-2 準備起飛。
Reinforcement drone in the air. The assault team is ready.
空中增援無人機。 突擊隊已準備就緒。
We are waiting for orders.
我們正在等待訂單。
Gönderin.
貢德林。
Dagger-2 in the air.
Dagger-2 在空中。
Dagger-3 in the air.
Dagger-3 在空中。
Dagger-4 in the air.
Dagger-4 在空中。
Komanchi, Dagger-1. Standard control.
科曼奇，匕首 1。 標準控制。
Komanchi 1-1, done.
Komanchi 1-1，完成。
The image is clean. I recommend Dagger go ahead.
圖像很乾淨。 我建議 Dagger 繼續。
Got it. We're going under the radar .
知道了。 我們正在雷達之下。
Dagger is under the radar right now.
匕首現在處於雷達之下。
I switch to snapshot.
我切換到快照。
Here we are. forward enemy territory.
我們到了。 前進敵方領土。
60 seconds to the limit.
60秒到極限。
Komanchi, Dagger-1. Image?
科曼奇，匕首 1。 圖片？
Komanchi, the image is clear. The decision is yours.
Komanchi，圖像清晰。 決定權在你。
Anlaşıldı.
Anlaşıldı。
Dagger, attack.
匕首，攻擊。
Tomahawks took off.
戰斧起飛。
There is no turning back anymore.
再也沒有回頭路了。
Daggers, let's move on to ﻿offensive formation .
匕首，讓我們繼續進攻陣型。
The Daggers have been replaced. We are moving towards the goal^
匕首已被替換。 我們正在朝著目標前進^
It starts at 2 minutes 30 seconds.
它從 2 分 30 秒開始。
3, 2, 1... started.
3、2、1……開始了。
- 2 okay. - 3 OK.
- 2 好吧。 - 3 好的。
4 ok.
4 好的。
Giriyoruz.
吉里約魯茲。
There are heat-seeking missiles ahead.
前方有尋熱導彈。
They don't work under the radar , Mav.
他們不會在雷達下工作，Mav。
Let's tie our rope to the solid stake.
讓我們把繩子系在堅固的木樁上。
More missiles on the hill.
山上的導彈更多。
We have 2 minutes left to the target.
我們距離目標還有 2 分鐘。
Got it. Time is running out, Rooster.
知道了。 時間不多了，公雞。
Hızlanmalıyız.
Hızlanmalıyız。
30 seconds for Tomahawks to land on the ﻿enemy airfield .
戰斧降落在敵方機場的時間為 30 秒。
Dagger, Komanchi. We're getting two enemy signals.
匕首，科曼奇。 我們收到兩個敵方信號。
It's right in front of us. Two contacts.
它就在我們面前。 兩個聯繫人。
Where did these come from?
這些是從哪裡來的？
Field patrol?
野外巡邏？
Komanchi, which way are they going?
Komanchi，他們要去哪條路？
Rotaları 0-9-0-5.
Rotaları 0-9-0-5。
- They're headed southwest. - They're moving away from us.
- 他們向西南方向前進。 - 他們正在遠離我們。
They don't know we are here.
他們不知道我們在這裡。
As those Tomahawks land at the airport, enemy planes will go to cover the target.
當那些戰斧降落在機場時，敵機將前往掩護目標。
We must be there before they arrive .
我們必須在他們到達之前到達那裡。
I increase the speed.
我提高速度。
We take care of you, Mav. Do not wait for me.
我們照顧你，馬夫。 不要等我。
Sir, Dagger 3 and 4 can't keep up.
長官，匕首 3 和 4 跟不上。
Arrival time at destination, 1 minute 20 seconds.
到達目的地時間，1分20秒。
3, 2...
3、2...
Düştüler!
杜施圖勒！
The enemy airbase was destroyed.
敵方空軍基地被摧毀。
They're all coming now.
他們現在都來了。
Enemies change direction towards the target.
敵人改變方向朝向目標。
Rooster, where are you
公雞，你在哪裡
Come on, Rooster! We have to make up for the time while we can!
加油，公雞！ 我們必須盡可能地彌補時間！
You heard the man.
你聽到了那個人。
Affedersin, Phoenix.
阿費德辛，鳳凰城。
Sir, the enemies are 2 minutes from the target.
長官，敵人距離目標只有 2 分鐘。
Daggers 1 minute away from target.
匕首離目標1分鐘。
Come on, Rooster. We will lose.
來吧，公雞。 我們會輸的。
Guys, we're lagging behind! We really need to speed up!
伙計們，我們落後了！ 我們真的需要加快速度！
If we don't accelerate now , those enemy planes...
如果我們現在不加速，那些敵機……
... it will be close ﻿when we reach the destination !
......當我們到達目的地時，它會很近！
Talk to me, dad.
跟我說話，爸爸。
Come on kid, you can do it. Thinking!
加油，孩子，你可以的。 思維！
Sadece yap!
薩迪斯耶！
Evet!
埃維特！
Looks like Rooster has decided to join us.
看起來公雞決定加入我們。
That's it, son. That's it!
就是這樣，兒子。 這就對了！
All right, we're leaving.
好吧，我們要走了。
Rooster, be slow!
公雞，慢點！
Sir, Dagger-2 is catching up.
長官，Dagger-2 正在迎頭趕上。
Hit your target and go home.
擊中目標並回家。
30 seconds to target. Prepare your laser.
30秒達到目標。 準備你的激光。
1-6-8-8 confirmation code, laser scanning completed.
1-6-8-8確認碼，激光掃描完成。
The lasers are ready!
激光準備好了！
Watch out for the heads.
注意頭部。
Hassiktir be!
哈西克提爾！
- Payback, are you with me? - I'm right behind you.
- 回報，你和我在一起嗎？ - 我就在你身後。
Phoenix, prepare to climb.
鳳凰，準備攀登。
Dagger-3 took its position.
Dagger-3 佔據了它的位置。
Tırmanmaya 3, 2, 1...
提爾曼瑪雅 3, 2, 1...
Hassiktir...
哈西克提爾...
Aim the laser, Bob.
瞄準激光，鮑勃。
Deniyorum...
否認...
- Stand by! - Come on Bob, come on!
- 支持！ - 來吧鮑勃，來吧！
Bekleyin
貝克萊因
Thank you! Send!
謝謝！ 發送！
Target detected. Bombs are on their way.
檢測到目標。 炸彈正在路上。
We hit him, Mav!
我們打了他，馬夫！
fuck it! Fuck!
去他媽的！ 他媽的！
The first miracle happened.
第一個奇蹟發生了。
Dagger-2, status report.
Dagger-2，狀態報告。
I'm about to arrive, Mav. I came!
我快到了，馬夫。 我來了！
Fanboy, where's my laser?
Fanboy，我的激光呢？
Rooster, I can't lock the laser!
公雞，我無法鎖定激光！
Siktir! From, from, from!
西克提爾！ 從，從，從！
Come on, guys! We're running out of time!
拜託了伙計們！ 我們的時間不多了！
I got it! I caught!
我知道了！ 我抓到！
Hassiktir!
哈西克提爾！
- Come on, Fanboy. Get it done! - No time. I'm going to shoot blind.
- 來吧，粉絲。 完成它！ - 沒時間。 我要瞎開槍了。
- Rooster, I'm on it. Wait! - There's no time left.
- 公雞，我在。 等待！ - 沒有時間了。
Bombs are on the way! bombs on the way
炸彈正在路上！ 炸彈在路上
It's 12! It's 12!
現在是 12 點！ 現在是 12 點！
Second miracle.
第二個奇蹟。
The corner of the coffin remained.
棺材的一角還在。
We're not done yet.
我們還沒有完成。
Here it begins.
從這裡開始。
Missiles took off! Phohenix, right behind you!
導彈起飛了！ 鳳凰，就在你身後！
Got it, I'm back!
知道了，我回來了！
Another one is coming!
又一個來了！
Dagger-1, on the defensive!
Dagger-1，處於防御狀態！
Rooster, status report?
公雞，狀態報告？
oh my god.
我的天啊。
Missiles took off!
導彈起飛了！ 導彈起飛了！
Right wing, Payback! Right wing!
右翼，報應！ 右翼！
Dönüyorum!
多努約魯姆！
oh my god! Coming!
我的天啊！ 未來！
How do we get rid of them?!
我們如何擺脫它們？！
I'm taking countermeasures!
我正在採取對策！
Themes were.
主題是。
Dagger-1 is descending.
Dagger-1 正在下降。
- Talk, Bob! - Turn, Phoenix! Frost!
- 說話，鮑勃！ - 轉身，鳳凰！ 霜！
in the direction of 9! 9!
9號的方向！  9！
Rooster, there are two more ﻿behind you!
公雞，你後面還有兩個！
Dagger-2 on the defensive!
Dagger-2 處於防御狀態！
Payback, put your nose down!
報應，放下你的鼻子！
Dagger-4 to 3, use your deflectors!
Dagger-4 到 3，使用你的導流板！
- Talk, Bob! - It's bad!
- 說話，鮑勃！ - 這是壞的！
- It's coming again! - We're busy here!
- 又來了！ - 我們在這裡很忙！
Dagger-2 on the defensive!
Dagger-2 處於防御狀態！
Fuck, I'm out of deflectors!
操，我的導流板用完了！
Rooster, Sallan! Sallan!
公雞，薩蘭！ 薩蘭！
I can't escape! They're after me, they're after me!
我無法逃脫！ 他們在追我，他們在追我！
No! No!
不！ 不！
Dagger-1 has been hit!
Dagger-1 被擊中！
I repeat, Dagger-1 has been hit!
我再說一遍，Dagger-1 被擊中了！
Maverick crashed.
小牛崩潰了。
Dagger-1, status report? Status report?
Dagger-1，狀態報告？ 狀況報告？
Has anyone seen him?
有人見過他嗎？ 有人見過他嗎？
- Dagger-1, answer! - I didn't see a parachute.
- Dagger-1，回答！  - 我沒有看到降落傘。
We need to go back.
我們需要回去。
Komanchi, the enemies are on their way.
Komanchi，敵人正在路上。
They come straight to you. Dagger is suggested to move south.
他們直接來找你。 建議匕首向南移動。
Enemies are heading south.
敵人正在南下。
Call them aboard now.
現在叫他們上船。
All Daggers advance to ECP . The ship is waiting for you.
所有匕首前進到ECP。 船在等你。
- What about Maverick? - Tell him there's nothing you can do for Maverick.
- 小牛呢？ - 告訴他你對 Maverick 無能為力。
- Not in an F-18. - Dagger-Reinforcement recovery mission requests confirmation.
- 不在 F-18 中。  - Dagger-Reinforcement 恢復任務請求確認。
Negative, Reinforcement.
負面，強化。
- Start search and rescue. - Negative. Not when the enemies are there.
- 開始搜救。 - 消極的。 不是在敵人在那裡的時候。
- Sir, Maverick is still there... - We're not going to lose anyone else today.
- 先生，Maverick 還在那裡... - 我們今天不會失去任何人。
Call them home now.
現在叫他們回家。
Dagger, don't make contact.
匕首，不要接觸。
I repeat, do not contact.
我再說一遍，不要聯繫。
Dagger-2, we're going home.
Dagger-2，我們要回家了。
come back. Turn back.
回來。 回頭。
Rooster, those enemies are approaching.
公雞，那些敵人正在逼近。
We can't go back.
我們不能回去。
Rooster.
公雞。
He died.
他死了。
Maverick is dead.
小牛已經死了。
Dagger-2 was shot down.
Dagger-2 被擊落。
Dagger-2, come in.
Dagger-2，進來。
Dagger-2, do you hear?
Dagger-2，你聽到了嗎？
Dagger-2, answer!
Dagger-2，回答！
- Are you okay? - Yes, I am good.
- 你還好嗎？ - 是的，我很好。
are you okay?
你還好嗎？
What are you doing?!
你在幹什麼？！
What are you doing here?
你在這裡做什麼？
- What am I doing? - You shoot that missile too...
- 我在做什麼？ - 你也發射那枚導彈……
... did I eat it to get shot? You should be on board right now!
……我吃它是為了中槍嗎？ 你現在應該上船了！
- I saved your life! - I saved your life.
- 我救了你的命！ - 我救了你的命。
That was the whole point.
這就是重點。
What was on your mind?
你在想什麼？
You're the one who said don't think!
你是那個說不要想的人！
Neyse...
奈斯...
It's good to see you.
真高興見到你。
Seni of.
塞尼。
So what's the plan?
那麼計劃是什麼？
You cannot be serious.
開玩笑吧。
You're goofing off, aren't you?
你在胡鬧，不是嗎？
An F-14?
F-14？
I had taken down three enemies ﻿on one of those things .
我在其中一件事上擊倒了三個敵人。
How do we know if ﻿that scrap can fly ?
我們怎麼知道廢料是否會飛？
Öğrenelim hadi.
Öğrenelim 哈迪。
Tamam.
塔瑪姆。
- There are men ahead. - Yes.
- 前面有男人。 - 是的。
- Let's not draw attention. - OK.
- 我們不要引起注意。 - 好的。
Let's start running. Run, come on!
讓我們開始跑步吧。 跑，來吧！
rooster When he gives you the signal...
公雞 當他給你信號時...
.. when the needle reaches 120 , turn the lever.
.. 當針達到 120 度時，轉動控制桿。
When the engine starts, all the pins and cables are removed.
當發動機啟動時，所有的針腳和電纜都被移除。
- Got it? - Yes.
- 知道了？ - 是的。
Evet!
埃維特！
Collect the ladder when you get up.
起床時收集梯子。
Tamam.
塔瑪姆。
Vay be...
萬事如意...
It's been a long time, huh Mav?
好久不見了，馬夫？
oh my god...
我的天啊...
This thing is very old.
這東西很老了。
Let's see.
讓我們來看看。
- Are you ready? - Ready.
- 你準備好了嗎？ - 準備好。
Even if the track isn't clean...
即使軌道不干淨...
...how do we ventilate this museum scrap ?
...我們如何為這個博物館廢料通風？
Wings from here, Mav.
來自這裡的翅膀，馬夫。
Mav, it's a taxiway.
馬夫，這是一條滑行道。
It's not the runway. You have a very narrow take- off area, Mav.
它不是跑道。 你有一個非常狹窄的起飛區域，馬夫。
You hold on tight.
你緊緊抓住。
Hassiktir be!
哈西克提爾！
Hadi, hadi, hadi!
哈迪，哈迪，哈迪！
I know you, come on.
我認識你，加油。
Mav?
馬夫？
Come on, some more!
來吧，再來點！
- Blue! - Here we go.
- 藍色的！ - 開始了。
Hassiktir be...
哈西克提爾...
Sir, we're picking up signals from Rooster's GPS.
先生，我們正在接收來自 Rooster 的 GPS 的信號。
It doesn't look like a malfunction.
看起來不像是故障。
- Did you lose him? - No, sir.
- 你失去他了嗎？ - 不，先生。
Supersonic right now.
現在超音速。
Havada.
哈瓦達。
- What is it in? - Sorry!
- 裡面有什麼？ - 對不起！
Information came from the tower that there was an F-14 ﻿heading towards our position .
來自塔台的信息表明有一架 F-14 正朝著我們的位置駛來。
This is impossible.
這是不可能的。
They can't.
他們不能。
Maverick.
特立獨行。
All right, Rooster. Contact the ship.
好的，公雞。 聯繫船舶。
Uğraşıyorum.
烏拉西約魯姆。
No wireless. There is no radar.
沒有無線。 沒有雷達。
Everything is dead here.
這裡的一切都死了。
What will I do? Tell me.
我該怎麼辦？ 告訴我。
Radio first. do something...
先說廣播。 做一點事...
UHF-2... circuit breaker.
UHF-2... 斷路器。
Onu dene.
奧努登。
Lots of weird circuits here. Any other details?
這裡有很多奇怪的電路。 還有其他細節嗎？
I don't know. It was your father 's department.
我不知道。 那是你父親的部門。
I solve it.
我解決它。
Mav, enemy aircraft below us.
小牛，我們下方的敵機。
what to do
該怎麼辦
OK, listen. act calm.
好的，聽著。 冷靜行事。
If they knew who we are , we'd be dead already.
如果他們知道我們是誰，我們早就死了。
Here they come.
他們來了。
Planın ne?
計劃嗎？
Let's put on our masks.
讓我們戴上面具吧。
Remember, we're on the same team.
請記住，我們在同一個團隊中。
Wave and smile.
揮手微笑。
What is this signal? What is he saying?
這是什麼信號？ 他在說什麼？
I don't know at all. I don't know what he says.
我根本不知道。 我不知道他說什麼。
What about this? Any idea?
那這個呢？ 任何想法？
No, I've never seen that either.
不，我也從未見過。
Hassiktir.
哈西克提爾。
They're trying to envelop us.
他們正試圖包圍我們。
OK, listen.
好的，聽著。
When I tell you, keep the rings on your head.
當我告訴你的時候，把戒指戴在你的頭上。
They're the launch rope.
它們是發射繩。
Mav, can we ﻿beat these guys
小牛，我們能打敗這些傢伙嗎
With loads of guns and missiles.
帶著大量的槍支和導彈。
Then there will be a dogfight.
然後會有一場混戰。
In an F-14? Against 5th generation warplanes?
在 F-14 中？ 對抗第五代戰機？
It's not on the plane, it's on the pilot.
它不在飛機上，它在飛行員身上。
If it wasn't for me, you'd be after them.
如果不是我，你會追上他們的。
But you are here.
但你在這裡。
Hadi, Mav.
哈迪，馬夫。
Düşünme.
杜松美。
Sadece yap.
Sadece 是的。
If you see a launch missile, tell me!
如果你看到發射導彈，告訴我！
- The missile has taken off! The missile took off! - Hold tight!
- 導彈起飛了！ 導彈起飛了！ - 抓緊！
Damn it, man! Someone's gone!
該死的，伙計！ 有人走了！
Another one is coming!
又一個來了！
Rooster, deflectors! Come on come on come on!
公雞，導流板！ 來吧來吧！
Get ready to cut gas!
準備好切斷天然氣！
Dönüyoruz!
多努尤魯茲！
- Now it's my turn. - On target, man! On target!
- 現在輪到我了。 - 目標，伙計！ 估計的正好！
I'm shooting!
我在射擊！
What was that?
那是什麼？
It's silly, what was that?
太傻了，那是什麼？
Hold tight! We will descend.
抓緊！ 我們將下降。
Rough terrain will confuse the targeting system.
崎嶇的地形會混淆目標系統。
Here it comes.
它來了。
Speak, Rooster. Where?
說吧，公雞。 在哪裡？
It's still after us.
它還在我們後面。
The fire is getting ready to open!
火已經準備好打開了！
damn it!
該死的！
Come on, man! Be a hero!
來吧，伙計！ 成為英雄！
Hold tight!
抓緊！
Hassiktir!
哈西克提爾！
On target! I open fire.
估計的正好！ 我開火。
damn it!
該死的！
Missiles are gone. I'm on the gun.
導彈沒了。 我在槍上。
Hadi, Mav. Hadi!
哈迪，馬夫。 哈迪！
- You can, man! - Once again.
- 你可以，伙計！ - 再次。
- One last chance. - You can do it.
- 最後一次機會。 - 你能行的。
Hadi, Maverick.
哈迪，特立獨行。
Yes! We're done!
是的！ 我們完了！
Mav, I turned on the radio.
馬夫，我打開收音機。
- Great. Communicate with the ship. - Understood.
- 偉大的。 與船溝通。 - 明白了。
oh my god.
我的天啊。
Where is this man?
這個人在哪裡？
right under our noses.
就在我們的眼皮底下。
Damn, we're out of ammo.
該死，我們的彈藥用完了。
The missile took off! Rooster, deflectors!
導彈起飛了！ 公雞，導流板！
This was so close!
這太近了！
We're out of deflectors, Mav.
我們的導流板用完了，小牛。
Shit, he's targeting us!
媽的，他是針對我們的！
This has not been good!
這一直不好！
- Mitchell, we're gonna get shot! - No no no!
- 米切爾，我們要中槍了！ - 不不不！
We can't take it anymore!
我們再也受不了了！
We ca n't escape ﻿this man . We have to throw it.
我們無法逃脫這個人。 我們必須扔掉它。
- What? - We need altitude.
- 什麼？ - 我們需要高度。
Pull the launch handle ﻿as soon as I tell you .
我一告訴你就拉發射把手。
- Mav, what...? - Rooster, you're leaving.
- 馬夫，什麼……？ - 公雞，你要走了。
Throw, throw, throw!
扔，扔，扔！
Rooster, pull the lever! Throw it!
公雞，拉動槓桿！ 丟它！
It doesn't work!
它不起作用！
Mav!
馬夫！
Üzgünüm.
烏茲古努姆。
Sorry, kid.
對不起，孩子。
No need to stand up , ladies and gentlemen.
女士們，先生們，無需站起來。
Your savior is speaking.
你的救主在說話。
Please fasten your seat belts and follow me home.
請係好安全帶，跟我回家。
And prepare to land.
並準備降落。
Hey, Hangman. You look good.
嘿，劊子手。 你看起來挺好的。
İyiyim, Rooster.
İyiyim，公雞。
I am very good.
我很好。
See you on board.
船上見。
Maverick goes against the wind. It has no front landing gear and no brakes.
特立獨行逆風而行。 它沒有前起落架，也沒有剎車。
Pull the rope for a hard stop.
拉繩子硬停。
All personnel on deck!
甲板上的所有人員！
Come on, walk!
來吧，走路！
Please don't tell me we lost ﻿an engine .
請不要告訴我我們失去了一個引擎。
OK, I won't tell you that.
好吧，我不會告訴你的。
Tamam.
塔瑪姆。
- Are you okay? - Yes.
- 你還好嗎？ - 是的。
İyiyim.
伊伊伊姆。
- You finally landed a plane in battle. - That's two.
- 你終於在戰鬥中降落了一架飛機。 - 那是兩個。
Maverick downloaded five.
小牛下載了五個。
That makes it second.
這使它成為第二。
Yüzbaşı Mitchell?
Yüzbaşı米切爾？
Efendim?
埃芬迪姆？
Thank you for ﻿saving my life .
謝謝你救了我的命。
My father would do the same.
我父親也會這樣做。
Hey, Mav.
嘿，馬夫。
Jimmy.
吉米。
Acaba...
阿卡巴...
Is Penny around?
佩妮在嗎？
They went on a boat trip ﻿with Emilia .
他們和艾米莉亞一起乘船旅行。
Did he say when he'll be back?
他有說什麼時候回來嗎？
No, he didn't.
不，他沒有。